<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>baalajimaestro</title>
    <link>https://baalajimaestro.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on baalajimaestro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Maestro Creativescape</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 21:24:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://baalajimaestro.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vendor Blob Extraction</title>
      <link>https://baalajimaestro.me/posts/extract-vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 21:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://baalajimaestro.me/posts/extract-vendor/</guid>
      <description>How to extract vendor blobs from stock rom? I got asked this question a lot, so I&amp;rsquo;ll post it here. Its gonna just be steps on how to do it.
⚠️ Note that you need a fully synced rom source for this.
 Place the Device Tree with the extract-files.sh inside.
 If your device tree doesn&amp;rsquo;t have an extract-files script, get it from github, its almost on every tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opensource and Monetization</title>
      <link>https://baalajimaestro.me/posts/opensource-and-monetisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 03:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://baalajimaestro.me/posts/opensource-and-monetisation/</guid>
      <description>Seems like these don’t go hand in hand, does it?
Lemme view it from my perspective.
Recently there was an android kernel developer who tried to monetize his kernel in the most inappropriate way possible. It became disastrous and he became a meme in that process. He was forced to leave development, forever.
So, is monetizing opensource software cancerous?
Red Hat is the global leader in open source software solutions — and has a clear strategy in how to generate revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git For Newbies</title>
      <link>https://baalajimaestro.me/posts/git-for-newbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 12:29:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://baalajimaestro.me/posts/git-for-newbies/</guid>
      <description>Before we start make sure git --version command successfully returns. If the output is something like command not found then please make sure Git is properly installed on your machine. My machine output is shown below. Output on your machine might be different.
 Commands that a user should type on his/her terminal are prefixed with the shell prompt symbol $. The output of command follows the command. Also, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to type $ on your terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$whoami</title>
      <link>https://baalajimaestro.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://baalajimaestro.me/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Baalaji Balasubramani, a 20 year old, popularly known around the internet world as baalajimaestro.
I work on Telegram UserBot and other opensource projects found on my GitHub.
I dualboot ArchLinux alongside Windows 10 (only for games xd). For programming, I use Python 3.7 as my primary choice. I can also code in C, C++, Java, Javascript, PHP, HTML5, CSS3. I am looking forward to learning Go and Rust. I use Bash Scripting to automate all tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://baalajimaestro.me/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://baalajimaestro.me/contact/</guid>
      <description>I would be available on Telegram almost all time except my sleep xD. Best would be ping me there for anything. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have Telegram, no problemo, you can reach me out on Instagram. For any formal correspondence, Email which has become too formal: baalajimaestro@computer4u.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>